Guide to the William S. Downing papers, 1922-2006.
Downing, William S. papers,
- Series V. Drawings
  - Young Residence, pre-1980; 39
  - Reconstruction Home, 1960; 40
    Project # 60-273
  - Danby Elementary, Engineering, 1961; 41
    Project # 322
  - Danby Elementary, Engineering, 1961; 42
  - Danby Elementary, 1961; 43
    Project # 61-322
  - Alterations to the Baron Steuben Hotel, 1961; 44
    Project # 9869-1901
  - Triangle Fraternity, 1961; 45
    Project # 324
  - Tioga Elementary, 1961; 46
    Project # 317-320
  - Tioga Elementary, Additions, 1961; 47
  - Tioga Elementary, Tioga Food Service, 1961; 48
    Project # 61-320
  - Tioga Kitchen Service, 49
    Project # 70
  - Tioga Central School, 1961; 49
    Project # 320
  - Tioga School, 49
  - Tioga Middle School, 49
  - Tioga Elementary School, Tioga Elementary Plumbing & ?, 1961; 50
  - Tioga Elementary School Addition, 1961; 50
    Project # 317
  - Tioga Elementary School Addition, 50
  - Tioga Elementary, 50
  - Watkins Glen State Park, Watkins Glen, New York, 1962; 51
    Project # 62-337
  - Watkins Glen Park, Watkins Glen, New York, 1962; 52
  - Watkins Glen Memorial Park, Blueprints of Existing Pavilion, Watkins Glen, New York, 1962; 53
  - Watkins Glen State Park Swimming Pool, Watkins Glen, New York, 1962; 54
  - Beta Symbol, A-13/14, 1961; 55
  - Ithaca Savings Bank, Ithaca, New York - Gibb & Waltz, Architects, 1922, 1961; 56
    Project # 61-331
  - #54 Alpha Epsilom Phi Renovations - Holt, Architect, 1941; 57
  - Ithaca Savings & Loan Renovations, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect, 1961; 57
  - Cayuga Lodge Renovations - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1960; 57
  - U.S. Post Office, Ithaca, New York, 1962; 58
  - U.S. Post Office, Ithaca, New York, 1964; 59
  - U.S. Post Office Addition, Ithaca, New York, 1962, 1986; 60
  - U.S. Post Office Feasibility Study, Ithaca, New York, 1986; 60
  - U.S. Post Office, Ithaca, New York, 1962; 61
  - Apartment Building for State and Aurora Inc., Ithaca, New York, 1965; 62
    Project # 377
  - Glen National Bank, Watkins Glen, New York, 1963; 63
    Project # 63-347
  - Chanango Valley State Park Boat House, 1963; 64
    Project # 63-351
  - Tuning Fork Square, 1969; 65
    Project # 69-437
  - Tioga Elementary, 1964; 66
  - Tioga Elementary, 1964; 66
  - Tioga Elementary School, 1964; 67
  - Chi Psi Fraternity, Ithaca, New York, 1964; 68
    Project # 363
  - Chi Psi Fraternity, Alterations and Renovations, Ithaca, New York - Wells/Koetter, Architects, 1968; 68
  - Ithaca High School, Ithaca, New York, 1964; 69
  - Ithaca High School, Ithaca, New York, 1964; 70
  - Alterations to 408 East State St., 1964; 71
    Project # 64-361
  - Alpha Delta Phi Add., 1964; 72
    Project # 64-368
  - First National Bank, Dryden, New York, 1964; 73
    Project # 376 (A)
  - Lake Erie State Park, 1965; 74
  - Lake Erie State Park, 1965; 75
  - Lake Erie State Park, 1965; 76
  - Lake Erie State Park Swimming Pool, 1965; 77
  - Big Flats Elementary, Horseheads, New York, 1965; 78
    Project # 373, 374
  - Big Flats Elementary, Horseheads, New York, 1965; 78
  - Seneca Lake State Park, 1965; 79
  - Seneca Lake State Park, 1965; 80
  - Gardner Elementary, 1965; 81
    Project # 65-374
  - FLAPC-Comfort Stations, 1965; 82
    Project # 65-385
  - Phi Gamma Delta, 1965; 83
    Project # 388
  - Ithaca Senior High School, Ithaca, New York, 1964; 84
  - Gardner Road Elementary, 1965; 85
  - Windsor Central School, 1966; 86
    Project # 66-398
  - Samson State Park, 1967; 87
    Project # 390
  - Samson State Park, 1967; 88
  - Samson State Park, 1967; 89
  - Samson State Park, 1967; 90
  - Samson State Park, 1967; 91
  - Golf House Samson State Park, 1967; 92
  - Lodi Point, Launching Site, Long Point, 1966; 93
  - Lodi Point, 1966; 94
  - Lod Point, Speias, Launching Site, 1966; 95
  - Ithaca Savings & Loan, Ithaca, New York, 1967; 96
    Project # 67-394
  - Skaneateles Lake, Launching Site, 1966; 97
    Project # 404-405
  - Skaneateles Lake State Marina Park, 1969; 97
  - Andes Swimming Pool, 1967; 98
    Project # 67-425
  - Tioga Central School Survey, 1970; 99
    Project # 1970-444
  - Tioga Central High School (Architectural), 1970; 100
    Project # 1970-445
  - Tioga Central High School (Engineering), 1970; 101
  - Tioga Central Middle School, 1970; 102
    Project # 1970-446
  - Tioga Central Middle School, 1970; 103
  - Tioga Elementary School Additions and Alterations, 1970; 104
    Project # 1970-447
  - New York State Department of Transportation Equipment and Maintenance Building, Hamburg, New York, 1970; 105
    Project # 1970-450
  - New York State Department of Transportation Equipment and Maintenance Building, Hamburg, New York, 1970; 106
  - New York State Department of Transportation Equipment and Maintenance Building, Hamburg, New York, 1970; 107
  - New York State Department of Transportation Equipment and Maintenance Building, Hamburg, New York, 1970; 108
  - New York State Department of Transportation Equipment and Maintenance Building, Hamburg, New York, 1970; 109
  - New York State Department of Transportation Equipment and Maintenance Building, Hamburg, New York, 1970; 110
  - Fair Haven Beach State Park, 1970; 111
    Project # 1970-452
  - Owego Professional Building, Owego, New York, 1971; 112
    Project # 1971-453
  - Owego Professional Building, Owego, New York, 1971; 113
  - Pearl Street Oakfield, 1971; 114
    Project # 1971-45X
  - Ithaca Gun Proposal, Ithaca, New York, 1972; 115
    Project # 1972-456
  - Ramada Inn, 1972; 116
    Project # 1972-457
  - Ramada Inn, 1972; 117
  - Ramada Inn, 1972; 118
  - Ramada Inn, 1972; 119
  - Ramada Inn, 1972; 120
  - Ramada Inn - First Floor Framing & Column Schedule, 1972; 121
  - Tompkins Country Trust Company Computer Center, 1972; 122
    Project # 1972-458
  - Monarch B-7/B-8, 1967; 123
    Project # 67-403
  - Monarch Engineering, 1967; 124
  - Auer Residence, 1967; 125
    Project # 67-407
  - Fscho, 1967; 126
  - Andes School Pool, 1967; 127
  - Danby Fire Station, 1968; 128
  - Lake Lauderdale State Park Original Survey, 1968; 129
    Project # 68-427
  - Lake Lauderdale State Park, 1968; 130
  - Lake Lauderdale State Park, 1969; 131
    Project # 69-427
  - Tuning Fork Building, Ithaca, New York, 1968; 132
  - Tuning Fork Building, Ithaca, New York, 1969; 133
    Project # 429
  - Tuning Fork Square, 1969; 133
  - Region II Headquarters Engineering, 1968; 134
  - Tuning Fork Building, Ithaca, New York, 1969; 135
    Project # 69-429
  - Finger Lakes State Park Comm. Administration Building Addition, 1969; 136
    Project # 69-434
  - Finger Lakes State Park Comm. Administration Building Addition, 1969; 137
  - Monarch Proposal, 1969; 138
    Project # 69-435
  - Monarch Proposal, 1969; 139
  - Hickories, 1969; 140
    Project # 69-439
  - Old Courthouse Renovation C-13/14, Ithaca, New York, 1973; 141
    Project # 1973-460
  - Old Courthouse Renovation, Ithaca, New York, 1973; 142
  - Old Courthouse Renovation C-13, Ithaca, New York, 1973; 143
  - Old Courthouse Renovation, Ithaca, New York, 1973; 144
  - Old Courthouse Renovation, Ithaca, New York, 1973; 145
  - Old Courthouse Renovation, Ithaca, New York, 1973; 146
  - Old Courthouse Renovation, Ithaca, New York, 1973; 147
  - Springwood, 1973; 148
    Project # 1973-461
  - DIVI Proposal, 1973; 149
    Project # 1973-462
  - Ramada Inn, Cortland, New York, 1973; 150
    Project # 1973-463
  - Tamarijh Beach Hotel, 1973; 151
    Project # 1973-464
  - Tamarijh Beach Hotel, 1973; 152
  - Tamarijh Beach Hotel, 1974; 153
    Project # 1974-464
  - Tamarijh Beach Hotel, 1974; 154
  - Renovation of Schooley Building, 1974; 155
    Project # 1974-465
  - NYS Warehouse #513 Staten Island Service Facility Division of Naval Affairs, 1974; 156
    Project # F762
  - NYS Warehouse #513 Staten Island Service Facility Division of Naval Affairs C-157, 1974; 157
    Project # 1974-467
  - Leighton/Hope Residence, 1974; 158
    Project # 1974-468
  - Leighton/Hope Residence A-15, 1974; 159
  - Baron Stuben Hotel, 1974; 160
    Project # 1974-470
  - Richmark Square, 1974; 161
    Project # 1974-472
  - Monarch Office Expansion, Cortland, NY, 1974; 162
    Project # 1974-473
  - Moog Incorporated Master Plan, 1975; 163
    Project # 1975-476
  - Moog Incorporated Master Plan A-6, 1975; 164
  - Moog Incorporated Master Plan, 1975; 165
  - Moog Incorporated Building 11A, 1975; 166
    Project # 1975-477
  - Moog Incorporated Building 11A, 1975; 167
    Project # 1974-477
  - Moog Incorporated Building 6, A-6, 1975; 168
    Project # 1975-478
  - Park Square with Wiggens Carport, 1975; 169
  - Park Square with Wiggens Carport, 1975; 169
    Project # 82-549
  - Moog Incorporated Building 11B, 1976; 170
    Project # 1976-482
  - Tompkins County Trust Company Drive Through Bank Center, Ithaca, New York, 1976; 171
    Project # 1976-484
  - Johnson City High School Conversions, 1976; 172
    Project # 1976-485
  - Johnson City High School Conversions - Drawings from originial 1967 King and King Building, 1976; 173
  - I.S.H.S. Changes to District Administration Building, 1976; 174
    Project # 1976-486
  - Ithaca High School Proposal, Ithaca, New York, 1993; 174
    Project # 486
  - Ithaca Senior High School Changes and Additions, Ithaca, New York, 174
  - Flinn Residence, 1977; 175
    Project # 1977-490
  - Flinn Residence, 1977; 176
  - Moog Incorporated Addition Proposal, 1977; 177
    Project # 1977-491
  - Leonard Wanzer Block/115 and 123 Cayuga Street Rest. Feasibility Study, 1977; 178
    Project # 1977-493
  - Leonard Wanzer Block/115 and 123 Cayuga Street Rest. Feasibility Study, 1977; 179
  - Moog Incorporated Plant #4, 1978; 180
    Project # 1978-498
  - Moog Incorporated Plant #4, 1978; 181
  - Carleton Controls, 1978; 182
    Project # 1978-500
  - Moog Incorporated Proner Airport, 1978; 183
    Project # 1978-503
  - Hoffman School Apartments, 1978; 184
    Project # 1978-504
  - Hoffman School Apartments, 1978; 185
  - Lincoln Apartments, 1978; 186
    Project # 1978-505
  - Lincoln Apartments, Revisions to Apartment Numbers 1 and 3, 2006; 186
  - Segnardi Office Building, Tioga Street, Ithaca, New York, 1978; 187
    Project # 1978-506
  - Egner Fire Station, Lansing, NY, 1978; 188
    Project # 1978-507
  - Watkins Glen Bay Hospital, Watkins Glen, NY, 1979; 189
    Project # 1979-509
  - Monarch Machine Tool Company Plant Addition, Cortland, NY, 1979; 190
    Project # 1979-511
  - Monarch Machine Tool Company Plant Addition, Cortland, NY, 1979; 191
  - Monarch Machine Tool Company Plant Addition, Cortland, NY, 1979; 192
  - Monarch Machine Tool Company Plant Addition, Cortland, NY, 1979; 193
  - Monarch Machine Tool Company Plant Addition, Cortland, NY, 1979; 194
  - Monarch Machine Tool Company Plant Addition, Cortland, NY, 1979; 195
  - Monarch Machine Tool Company Plant Addition, Cortland, NY, 1979; 196
  - Monarch Machine Tool Company Plant Addition, Cortland, NY, 1979; 197
  - Monarch Machine Tool Company Plant Addition, Cortland, NY, 1979; 198
  - Trumansburg School District Re-Roofing, 1979; 199
    Project # 1979-512
  - Schoolhouse Manor, 1980; 200
    Project # 1980-516
  - Schoolhouse Manor, 1980; 201
  - Schoolhouse Manor, 1980; 202
  - Moog Incorporated, 1980; 203
    Project # 1980-519
  - Moog Incorporated, 1980; 204
  - Moog Incorporated, 1980; 205
  - East Hill School Rehabilitation Project, Ithaca, New York, 1980; 206
    Project # 1980-520
  - Strand Theater, Ithaca, New York, 1980; 207
    Project # 1980-523
  - Strand Theater, Ithaca, New York, 1980; 208
  - Strand Theater, Ithaca, New York, 1980; 209
  - Moog Incorporated Building 2A, 1980; 210
    Project # 1980-524
  - Valentine Dormitory, 1980; 211
    Project # 1980-524A
  - Tompkins County Memorial Hospital, Alterations to Biggs Memorial Hospital, 1980; 212
    Project # 1980-525
  - Tompkins County Memorial Hospital, Alterations to Biggs Memorial Hospital - Holt, Architect, 1957; 213
    Project # 265
  - Central Avenue Development, Parking Study Proposal, 1981; 214
    Project # 1981-527
  - Central Avenue Development, Parking Study Proposal, 1981; 215
  - Tamarijh Dining Pavilion, 1981; 216
    Project # 1981-530
  - Clute Cottage, 1981; 217
    Project # 1981-533
  - Brown Cottage Tamiami Homestead, 1981; 218
    Project # 1981-536
  - Cortland County Court House, Cortland, NY, 1981; 219
    Project # 1981-538
  - Cortland County Court House, Cortland, NY, 1981; 220
  - Trumansburg Central School Dust Collector, Trumansburg, NY, 1981; 221
    Project # 1981-542
  - Aruba Beach Hotel, 1981; 222
    Project # 1981-540
  - Medical Office Building Property, 1981; 223
    Project # 1981-543
  - Dutch Village Aruba, 1981; 224
    Project # 1981-547
  - Dutch Village Aruba, 1981; 225
  - Dutch Village Aruba, 1981; 226
  - Dutch Village Aruba, 1981; 227
  - Tamarijh Dance Floor, 1982; 228
    Project # 1982-546
  - Wong Apartments, 1982; 229
    Project # 1982-548
  - Ithaca College Service Building, Ithaca, New York, 1982; 230
    Project # 1982-551
  - Ithaca College Service Building, Ithaca, New York, 1982; 231
  - "Harborside" Cayuga Inlet & Island Redevelopment Plan, B-12, Ithaca, New York, 1982; 232
    Project # 1982-553
  - Ramada Tower, 1982; 233
    Project # 1982-554
  - Ramada Tower, 1982; 234
  - Ramada Tower, 1982; 235
  - Ramada Tower, 1982; 236
  - Ramada Tower, 1982; 237
  - Tiara Beach Hotel, 1983; 238
    Project # 1983-559
  - Tiara Beach Hotel, 1983; 239
  - Tiara Beach Hotel, 1983; 240
  - Tech A1-E1, 1983; 241
    Project # 1983-561
  - Tompkins County Library Renovation, Ithaca, New York, 1983; 242
    Project # 1983-563
  - Snyder Residence, 1983; 243
    Project # 1983-564
  - Yauht Club, 1983; 244
    Project # 1983-566
  - Tompkins County Office Complex, 1983; 245
    Project # 1983-569A
  - 200 Tioga Street, Ithaca, New York - O'Brian & Taube, Architects, 1983; 246
    Project # 1983-569B
  - 200 Tioga Street, Ithaca, New York - O'Brian & Taube, Architects, 1983; 247
  - Rutledge Residence, 1983; 248
    Project # 1983-567
  - Moog Incorporated Office for William Moog, 1984; 249
    Project # 1984-572
  - Moog Incorporated Office for William Moog, 1984; 250
  - Moog Incorporated Office for William Moog, 1984; 251
  - Hanger Theater, Ithaca, New York and College Ave., Ithaca, New York, 1984; 252
    Project # 1984-572A
  - Hanger Theater, Ithaca, New York, 1984; 253
  - Tomkin's County Trust Company Drive Through Bank Center, Ithaca, New York, 1976; 254
    Project # 1984-484
  - Moog, 1984; 255
  - Tompkins County Library Renovation, Ithaca, New York, 1983; 256
    Project # 1983-562
  - Monarch Machine Tool Company Additions, 1984; 257
    Project # 1984-573
  - Hoy Field, Parking and Planning Study, 1984; 258
    Project # 1984-578
  - Women's Community Building, Ithaca, New York, 1984; 259
    Project # 1984-581
  - Women's Community Building, Ithaca, New York, 1986; 259
    Project # 1986-610
  - Delavan Residence, 1984; 260
    Project # 1984-582
  - Delavan Residence, 1984; 261
  - Snee Hall, Cornell University, Ithaca, New York, 1984; 262
    Project # 1984-583
  - Ithaca Youth Bureau, Ithaca, New York, 1984; 263
    Project # 1984-584
  - Ithaca Youth Bureau, Ithaca, New York, 1984; 264
  - Ithaca Youth Bureau, Ithaca, New York, 1984; 265
  - Ithaca Youth Bureau, Ithaca, New York, 1984; 266
  - Ithaca Youth Bureau, Ithaca, New York, 1984; 267
  - Tobin Field House, Cornell University, Ithaca, New York, 1984; 268
    Project # 1984-585
  - Tobin Field House, Cornell University, Ithaca, New York, 1984; 269
  - Housing and Parking Complex, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect, 1984; 270
    Project # 1984-xxx
  - New York State Armory, Dryden, New York, 1985; 271
    Project # 1985-588
  - New York State Armory, Dryden, New York, 1985; 272
  - Kromhahsl Residence, 1985; 273
    Project # 1985-591
  - Black Oak Lane, 1985; 274
    Project # 1985-592
  - Black Oak Lane, 1985; 275
  - Black Oak Lane, 1985; 276
  - Black Oak Lane, 1985; 277
  - Black Oak Lane, 1985; 278
  - Black Oak Lane, 1985; 279
  - Black Oak Lane, 1985; 280
  - Black Oak Lane, 1985; 281
  - Black Oak Lane, 1985; 282
  - Black Oak Lane, 1985; 283
  - Black Oak Lane, 1985; 284
  - Black Oak Lane, 1985; 285
  - Nee Residence, 1985; 286
    Project # 1985-593
  - Perkins Residence, 1985; 287
    Project # 1985-594
  - Perkins Residence, 1985; 288
  - P.T. Wood Offices, 1985; 289
    Project # 1985-595
  - P.T. Wood Offices, 1985; 290
  - G. Bailey Insurance, C.13, 1985; 291
    Project # 1985-596
  - G. Bailey Insurance, C.13, 1985; 292
  - Zwickel Residence, 1985; 293
    Project # 1985-597
  - Mountainside Villas Owners Association, Winchester, Virginia, 1985; 294
    Project # 1985-599
  - Mountainside Villas Owners Association, Winchester, Virginia, 1985; 295
  - Mountainside Villas Owners Association, Winchester, Virginia, 1985; 296
  - Mountainside Villas Owners Associatio A18., Winchester, Virginia, 1985; 297
  - Mountainside Villas Owners Association, Winchester, Virginia, 1985; 298
  - Student Agencies, 1985; 299
    Project # 1985-601
  - Guckenheimer Residence, C.21, 1986; 300
    Project # 1986-604
  - Guckenheimer Residence, C.21, 1986; 301
  - Guckenheimer Kusch Residence, C.21, 1986; 302
  - Guckenheimer Residence, 1986; 303
  - Guckenheimer Residence, 1986; 304
  - Mayer School, 1986; 305
    Project # 1986-605
  - Day Treatment Facility, J.N. Adam Developmental Center, 1986; 306
    Project # 1986-608
  - J.N. Adam Development Center, Perrysburg, New York, 1950; 307
  - J.N. Adam Development Center, Perrysburg, New York, 1986; 308
  - J.N. Adam Development Center, Perrysburg, New York, 1986; 309
  - J.N. Adam Development Center, Perrysburg, New York, 1986; 310
  - J.N. Adam Development Center, Perrysburg, New York, 1986; 311
  - J.N. Adam Development Center, Perrysburg, New York, 1986; 312
    Project # 1986-609
  - J.N. Adam Development Center, Perrysburg, New York, 1986; 313
  - J.N. Adam Development Center, Perrysburg, New York, 1986; 314
  - J.N. Adam Development Center, Perrysburg, New York, 1986; 315
  - J.N. Adam Development Center, Perrysburg, New York, 1986; 316
  - Ithaca Youth Bureau, Ithaca, New York, 1984; 317
  - Moog - Space Products Division, 1986; 318
    Project # 1986-613
  - Moog - Space Products Division, 1986; 319
  - Ciaschi Building, 1987; 320
    Project # 1987-614
  - Ciaschi Building, 1987; 321
  - Ciaschi Building, 1987; 322
  - Ciaschi Building, 1987; 323
  - Ciaschi Building, 1987; 324
  - Ciaschi Building, Tracings, B-24, 1987; 325
  - Ciaschi Building, B-24, 1987; 326
  - Ciaschi Building, Tracings, B-24, 1987; 327
  - Ciaschi Building, Prints B-24, 1987; 328
  - Ciaschi Building, Prints B-24, 1987; 329
  - Ithaca Child Care Center, Ithaca, New York, 1987; 330
  - Ithaca Child Care Center, Ithaca, New York, 1994; 330
    Project # 94-694
  - Ithaca Child Care Center, Ithaca, New York, 1987; 331
  - Tompkins County Mental Health Services Building, 1988; 332
    Project # 88-643
  - Ramada Remodeling, 1987; 333
    Project # 1987-622
  - Ramada Remodeling, 1987; 334
  - Ramada Remodeling, 1987; 335
  - Ramada Remodeling, 1987; 336
  - Herson Residence, 1988; 337
  - Sears Residence, 1988; 338
  - Sears Residence, 1988; 339
  - Dyckman Residence, 1988; 340
  - Wilson Residence, 1988; 341
    Project # 88-630
  - Dykman Residence, 1988; 342
  - Tompkins County Chamber of Commerce, 1988; 343
  - Tompkins County Chamber of Commerce, 1988; 344
    Project # 88-663
  - Seneca Lake State Park, 1965; 345
  - Lakewatch Drive Development, 1988; 346
    Project # 88-637(B)
  - Tompkins County Library, Ithaca, New York, 1988; 347
    Project # 88-642
  - Tompkins County Library, Ithaca, New York, 1988; 348
  - Tompkins County Mental Health Services Building, 1988; 349
  - Tompkins County Mental Health Services Building, 1988; 350
  - Tompkins County Mental Health Services Building, 1988; 351
  - Tompkins County Mental Health Services Building, 1988; 352
  - St. John's Church, 1988; 353
    Project # 88-650
  - St. John's Church, 1988; 354
  - United Way, 1989; 355
  - Industrial Building for Deanco, Lansing, New York, 1989; 356
    Project # 89-659(A)
  - Tompkins County Courthouse, Ithaca, New York, 1990; 357
    Project # 90-65?
  - Hay's Garage, Flinn Barn Innkeeper Quarters, 1990; 358
    Project # 90-659
  - Gifft Residence, 1990; 359
  - Gifft Residence, 1990; 360
  - Gifft Residence, A-19, 1990; 361
  - Gifft Residence, A-19, 1990; 362
  - Gifft Residence, A-19, 1990; 363
  - Gifft Residence, 1990; 364
  - Gifft Residence, A-19, 1990; 365
  - Gifft Residence, A-19, 1990; 366
  - Gifft Residence, 1990; 367
  - Yacht Club Proposal, June 1, 1991; 368
  - Advantage Auto, 1990; 369
    Project # 90-662
  - Bayhorse B&B, 369
  - Talbots, Triphammer Cinema, 1991; 369
    Project # 91-667
  - Talbots Triphammer Cinema, 1991; 370
  - United Methodist Church, 1992; 371
    Project # 92-666
  - Torcotte Residence, 1992; 372
  - Torcotte Residence, 1992; 373
  - Schreiner Residence, 1992; 374
    Project # 92-671(B)
  - Gardner Residence, 1992; 375
  - Gardner Residence - Renovations, 1999; 375
    Project # 99-765
  - Community Residence Willard DAAA, John Miller's House Design, 1992; 376
    Project # 92-673
  - Condohotel Cancun, A-24, 1993; 377
    Project # 93-674
  - Walmart Proposal, 1993; 378
    Project # 93-675 (Miscellaneous)
  - Cabin Fever Festival (Miscellaneous), 1993; 379
    Project # 93-676
  - Buttermilk Valley, C-15, 1993; 380
    Project # 93-678
  - Code of Compliance, 1993; 381
    Project # 93-679
  - Kazda Residence, 1993; 382
    Project # 93-680
  - Blacksburg Civic Activities Center (Miscellaneous), 1993; 383
  - Community Residence - Prints, 1993; 384
  - Community Residence, 1993; 385
  - Community Residence, 1993; 386
  - L'Auberge DH Cochon Rouge, ithaca, New York, 1994; 387
    Project # 94-683
  - Drop-In Children's Center, 1994; 388
  - Drop-In Children's Center, 1994; 389
  - Drop-In Children's Center - Record Set & Miscellaneous, 1994; 390
  - Drop-In Children's Center, 1994; 391
  - Country Club, 1994; 392
  - Deer Run, Existing, A-24, 1994; 393
    Project # 94-690
  - Deer Run, Ithaca, New York, 1994; 394
  - Downtown Development: TCTC Drive Thru; Post-Office Remodel, Ithaca, New York, 1994; 395
    Project # 94-691
  - Lakeside Nursing Home, Trumansburg, NY, 1994; 396
  - Lakeside Nursing Home - As Built Set: Velums, Trumansburg, NY, 1994; 397
  - Lakeside Nursing Home - As Built Set: Prints, Trumansburg, NY, 1994; 398
  - Lakeside Nursing Home, Trumansburg, NY, 1994; 399
  - Egner Fire Station, 1995; 400
    Project # 95-000
  - Corning YMCA, Corning, New York, 1995; 401
    Project # 95-700
  - Walck Residence - First Bid Set, Bradford County, Pennsylvania, 1995; 402
    Project # 95-702
  - Walck Residence, Bradford County, Pennsylvania, 1995; 403
  - Bridges of Ithaca - Classen, Ithaca, New York, 1996; 404
    Project # 96-707
  - Bridges of Ithaca - Classen, Ithaca, New York, 1996; 405
  - Montour House - Record Set, 1997; 406
    Project # 97-719
  - Walck Residence, 1996; 407
    Project # 96-
  - Cornell Feasibility Study - Shuffle II, 1997; 408
    Project # 97-728
  - Christian Scientist Church, 1997; 409
  - Day Hall, Registrar, Cornell University, Ithaca, New York, 1997; 410
  - Hollister Hall, Cornell University, Ithaca, New York, 411
  - Day Hall, Registrar Cornell University, Ithaca, New York, 1997; 412
  - Day Hall, Human Relations, Cornell University, Ithaca, New York, 2000; 412
  - Day Hall, 2nd Floor, Cornell University, Ithaca, New York, 2001; 412
    Project # 01-817
  - Day Hall, Human Resources, Cornell University, Ithaca, New York, 2001; 412
  - City Hall, Ithaca, New York, 2001; 412
    Project # 01-819
  - Schurman Hall, Cornell University, Ithaca, New York, 1998; 412